[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Hurry!
[Baggage Keeping Area]
Looks like he hasn't gone far.
We must find him as soon as possible
and bring him back for the experiment.
[Apocalypse Log 11]
[Baggage Keeping Area]
They're looking for someone.
They're looking for you.
Why are they looking for you?
They're from Casia.
After the apocalypse,
they forced me to research the zombie virus.
I barely managed to escape.
I don't want to be captured by them again.
You research the zombie virus?
They're still nearby.
Let's talk later.
Since there's no fuel at T1, why don't we check T2?
Let's go.
Looking at the path we've taken,
it doesn't look like anyone's lived here.
But don't worry.
Your brother most likely took refuge somewhere else.
Let's find fuel first.
We can leave once we find it.
I'll look for him elsewhere, too.
He, you said it's all the same after the apocalypse.
What did you mean?
After the apocalypse, Casia partnered with armed groups.
They provide protection,
but they also keep the lab locked down like a fortress.
People like me
are no different from high-profile prisoners.
The research direction isn't for us to decide.
Has there been any actual progress?
There are some theoretical models.
But as for a real antibody, we're still a long way off.
Did you find it?
Nothing here.
I'll check over there.
Keep it down, or you'll attract zombies.
What's there to fear? It'll be good practice.
He Yao.
Let's go.
Lie, run!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
There are two more people over there.
Wait for me here.
Let's go.
He Yao, that bastard.
So, he wanted to steal our car.
Let's get out of this airport first.
It's okay.
You're safe now.
It's all right now.
Where are we?
In the car.
I'm not so far gone that I can't recognize a car.
I mean...
Where are you taking me?
To find a place to settle you in.
Then we'll figure something out.
Don't feed me your blood ever again.
He Yao.
You still won't give up?
I will never give up.
Not until I'm dead.
I'm the one who's dead.
Haven't you faced reality yet?
You're not like them.
You're just sick.
He Yao.
Don't try to cure me...
just to prove that you're better than me.
I admit defeat, okay?
Then the loser should listen to the winner.
I'm a zombie.
I could bite you at any moment.
Why do you insist on staying with a living dead like me?
Drop your damn competitive streak.
I'm not the competitive one here.
You're the one who wanted to beat me...
so you experimented on yourself and ended up like this.
This was my own choice.
I'll bear the consequences.
It has nothing to do with you.
Well, this is my choice.
And I'll bear it myself.
You're crazy.
I've been fucking crazy for a long time.
Fine.
Lie.
You have a fever.